https://themusicresource.com/privacy-policy/

Back to top
———–At TheMusicResource.com we are dedicated to protecting your data and privacy.We recognize that your privacy is important.
This document outlines the types of personal information we receive and collect
when you use TheMusicResource.com, as
well as some of the steps we take to safeguard information. This will help you
make an informed decision about sharing personal information with us.TheMusicResource.com strives to maintain the highest standards of decency,
fairness and integrity in all our operations. Likewise, we are dedicated to
protecting our customers’ and online visitors’ privacy on our website.Table of Contents
About Our CookiesGoogle Analytics CookiesAdvertising
CookiesAffiliate Products and ServicesRetargeting
Ads and Tracking Pixels Refusing CookiesPersonally Identifiable
InformationNon-personally Identifiable
InformationChildren’s Privacy ProtectionRelease of InformationData StorageHow You Can Correct or Remove
InformationUpdates and Effective DateAgreeing to TermsAbout Our CookiesA cookie is a string of information that TheMusicResource.com stores on your
computer, which your browser provides to TheMusicResource.com each time you return to the site. We use cookies to help us identify and
track visitors, their use of our website, and their website access preferences.Google Analytics CookiesTheMusicResource.com uses Google Analytics to analyze the use of this
website. Google Analytics collects demographic and interest data, and generates
statistical and other information about website use, by means of cookies. These
cookies are kept on your computer. We share this information with Google, which
will store and use this information on its servers. Google’s privacy policy is
available at: https://policies.google.com/privacyTheMusicResource.com uses information from Google Analytics to track the
number of visits to the website, browsers and operating systems. No personally
identifiable information is obtained from these cookies. We use the information
that Google Analytics generates relating to our website to create reports about
the use of the site. These reports allow us to update the site and improve your
usage of it.If you do not wish
your data to be collected via Google Analytics, you can install its opt-out
browser extension or add-on…https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/Advertising
CookiesWe use third-party
advertising companies to serve ads on our website. These companies use cookies
and web beacons in their ads to ascertain how many times you’ve seen an
advertisement. We share this information with these companies, but do not
provide them with any personally identifiable information for cookie or web
beacon use, so they cannot personally identify you with that information from
our website.You may opt out of
personalized ads for over 125 different ad networks. Click the following link
to do that… http://www.aboutads.info/choices/Some third-party
advertisements are served by Google. Google’s cookie enables it to serve ads to
our visitors based on their visits to other sites on the Web. You may opt out
of personalized ads by visiting the Google ad opt-out page… https://adssettings.google.com/authenticatedThis link from
Google provides more information about how Google manages data in its ad
products… https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sitesAffiliate Products and ServicesWe receive an
affiliate commission for some of the products/services sold on TheMusicResource.comThe affiliate
services platforms we use are Amazon,
ShareASale, ClickBank, Commission Junction, etc.By clicking on a
product or service link, you consent to that platform’s use of cookies, as
outlined in the link below.https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496 https://skimlinks.com/privacy-policies/Retargeting
Ads and Tracking Pixels TheMusicResource.com uses retargeting ads, which require the setting of
cookies in your browser.TheMusicResource.com uses Facebook pixels to determine the effectiveness
of some Facebook ad campaigns. You can change your Facebook ad settings here… https://www.facebook.com/ads/preferences/?entry_product=ad_settings_screenRefusing CookiesYou can set your browser to accept or refuse
all cookies automatically, or notify you when a cookie is being requested.
Taking this action should not cause a problem with the continued use of our
site. Consult the Help section of your browser for guidance on how to refuse
all cookies or to notify you when a cookie is requested.If you choose to refuse TheMusicResource.com‘s cookies, you may not be able to fully experience
the interactive features of the site.Personally Identifiable
InformationTheMusicResource.com may collect and use your personal information for the
following purposes:To run and operate our site.To display content on the site
correctly.To improve customer service.To help us respond to your
customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.To personalize your user
experience.To understand how our users as a
group use the services and resources provided on our site.To improve our site.To improve our products and
services.To run a promotion, contest,
survey or other site feature.To send information to you that
you agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to you.To send periodic emails, which may
include electronic newsletters and/or autoresponder series of emails.To respond to your enquiries,
questions, and/or other requests.TheMusicResource.com may collect personally identifiable information from
you in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when you visit our
site, register on the site, or fill out a form, and in connection with other
activities, services, features or resources we make available on our site.Specifically, if
you subscribe to our newsletter, we will ask for your first name and will
require your email address.If you complete a
form, we will require your name and your email address, and will ask for
information relevant to the purpose of the form.This site also uses
Facebook commenting. Facebook stores all of your comments and may show them on
your timeline, depending on your Facebook settings.You can always refuse to supply personally
identifiable information and visit our site anonymously. However, it may
prevent you from engaging in certain site-related activities.If we make material changes in the collection
of personally identifiable information, we will inform you by placing a notice
on our site. We will use personal information received from you for internal
purposes only and will not sell it or provide it to third parties.We also collect each visitor’s IP address,
which helps us combat spam and fraud. We do not use IP addresses for any other
purpose.Non-personally Identifiable
InformationWe may collect non-personally identifiable
information about you whenever you interact with our site. Non-personally
identifiable information may include the browser name, the type of computer and
technical information about your method of connecting to our site, such as the
operating system and the Internet service provider you used, and other similar
information.Children’s Privacy ProtectionThis website is directed to adults. It is not
directed to children under the age of 16. We operate our site in compliance
with current regulations. Anyone under the age of 16 must provide parental
consent to use this site. We do not knowingly collect or use personally
identifiable information from anyone under 16 years of age.Release of InformationIf we sell TheMusicResource.com, the information we have obtained from you
through your voluntary participation in our site may transfer to the new owner
as a part of the sale so that the service provided to you may continue. In that
event, you will receive notice through our website of that change in control
and practices, and we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purchaser
honors any opt-out requests you might make.Data StoragePersonally identifiable information and
non-personally identifiable information collected by this site is stored on our
host’s servers.How You Can Correct or Remove
InformationWe provide this privacy policy as a statement
to you of our commitment to protect your personally identifiable information.
If you have submitted personally identifiable information through our website
and would like to update that information or have it deleted from our records, contact
us.Updates and Effective DateTheMusicResource.com reserves the right to make changes in this policy. If
there is a material change in our cookie and privacy practices, we will
indicate on our site that those practices have changed and provide a link to
the updated privacy policy. We encourage you to periodically review this policy
so that you will know what information we collect and how we use it.Agreeing to TermsIf you do not agree to TheMusicResource.com‘s privacy policy as posted here on this
website, please do not consent to the setting of cookies and the collection and
storage of your personally identifiable information.Your explicit consent indicates acceptance of
this privacy policy in its entirety.Last updated: 12-09-19.
Recent Posts How Hard Is It To Learn The Piano? What Are Dynamics In Music? — Detailed Answer Shure SE215 Vs SE315 – Detailed Comparison What Is Contemporary Music? How Much Do Piano Lessons Cost?CategoriesAcoustic GuitarsDigital PianosMicrophoneQuestionsUncategorizedAffiliate DisclosureWe have affiliate relationships with the providers (Amazon, Clickbank, etc) of the products, goods and services that are linked to on this page and may be compensated when you buy. But do note that it doesn't increase the cost of the products to you in any way or determine our verdict on a product/service. We use cookies to collect and analyse information on site performance and usage, and to enhance and customize content and advertisements. By clicking "I agree" or by clicking into any content on this site, you agree to allow cookies to be placed. To find out more or to change your cookie settings, visit the cookies section of our privacy policy. Cookie settingsI AGREEPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Always EnabledNecessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessaryAny cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
